

# **Teng Min**

Full Stack | Blockchain Dev itdeveloper724@gmail.com

### Introduction

Talented senior software engineer with strong experience in dApp development and worked on various projects over the last 8 years.

As a senior full stack and blockchain developer, I am expertized in creating smart contracts and developed many professional Defi, DEX and DAO platforms on EVM based networks, Solana and Cosmos network.

With the big booming of NFT market, I am also deeply engaged in NFT platform development and doing continuous research on top trend blockchain technologies. With the long experience in software development, I have the sufficient qualifications and capabilities to develop project from scratch to release. I am a creative problem solver and like to working with good team members and share new ideas for the progress.

## Work experience

#### Professional Blockchain Developer

Freelancer / Self-employed (Nov 2020 - Now)

- Build Defi, Auto staking project, Crypto mining project on EVM networks
- Develop Presale, ICO, smart contracts for Launch Pad, DAO
- Develop and launched NFT minting, staking platforms and Marketplaces with smart contracts on Ethereum and Solana, etc.

#### Senior Web Developer

Mobiloitte in Singapore (Jan 2018-Oct 2020)

- Developed dApp with building the frontend and integrating by web3.js
- Developed and audited smart contracts for token and NFT creation.
- Built Cryptocurrency Exchange/Trading system, Defi.

#### **Senor Web Developer**

NEU ENTITY in Singapore. (Oct 2017 - Apr 2019)

- Delivered eCommerce sites using GIS technologies and AWS W
- Developed membership systems using Node.js, React.js, React-Redux, Svelte and Typescript
- Developed the frontend of blockchain dApps and integration
- Developed eCommerce with Django, Node.js, Express.js, PHP, Laravel.

#### Web Developer

Wired Craft in Hong Kong. (Feb 2015 – Jun 2017)

- Developed eCommerce using EXT.js and Spring framework
- Developed UI templates for AI projects using React.js.
- Developed React components from Figma.

#### **Education**

Bachelor of Computer Science, Fudan University

From May 2010 to June 2014

- Developed a faculty management project to organize lectures.
- Member of Computer laboratory in science

**Ethereum** Solidity **Smart Contract NFT** Solana Rust Defi DEX DAO Web3.js Ether.js **GraphQL Token Development** React.js Vue.js MySQL, MongoDB Unity & C# **Android** PHP, CI, Laravel, YII

Skill

Django